<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Soliloquy Fun Blog</title>
    <link>https://soliloquy.fun/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Soliloquy Fun Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Soliloquy Fun Blog</title>
      <url>https://soliloquy.fun/assets/images/soliloquy-card.png</url>
      <link>https://soliloquy.fun/assets/images/soliloquy-card.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://soliloquy.fun/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Soliloquy?</title>
      <link>https://soliloquy.fun/blog/posts/what-is-soliloquy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soliloquy.fun/blog/posts/what-is-soliloquy/</guid>
      <description>Soliloquy refers to the act of speaking one&amp;rsquo;s thoughts aloud, whether alone or in the presence of others. It&amp;rsquo;s a technique often used by characters in plays to convey their innermost emotions and ideas.
Now, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share that I&amp;rsquo;ve developed a new mobile application that can help you learn foreign languages by speaking! If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in trying the beta version of the app, please sign up for our waiting list by clicking here: join waiting list !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn a foreign language in 1 year - The Soliloquy approach</title>
      <link>https://soliloquy.fun/blog/posts/learn-a-foreign-language-in-1-year-the-soliloquy-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://soliloquy.fun/blog/posts/learn-a-foreign-language-in-1-year-the-soliloquy-approach/</guid>
      <description>Remember those times when you were about to talk to someone in a different language, but you were so nervous and stressed that you couldn&amp;rsquo;t speak. Whereas, in your head, you can even think in a different language, or you can understand a vast amount of videos you watch on the internet. But you still have difficulty speaking.
I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced that too, more than I can count. Whether it was back in high school facing that final English exam, or even at work, trying to talk to clients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
